https://christiancommunity.org.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy | New Creation Christian Community
HomeAbout NCCCArticlesChallenge and inspirationPeople’s StoriesInterviewsMultimediaVideosBooksSuggested ReadingLinks To Christian Communities
Privacy PolicyHome › Privacy PolicyThe website address is christiancommunity.org.uk.We are committed to protecting your privacy and we will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and EU General Data Protection Regulation 2016).What personal data we collect and why we collect it Contact formsWhen visitors submit a query through our contact form we collect the data shown in the form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.CookiesCookies help us understand who our visitors are and what they like to browse, and therefore they help us to customise and improve your experience of our website. They don’t allow us to personally identify any visitors and are not harmful to you or your computer/device. You can block cookies by activating settings in your browser that refuse some or all cookies. If you do so you may not be able to access parts or features of our site.If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.Embedded content from other websitesPages on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, audio, maps, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website. Please refer to the privacy policies of the providers of any embedded media you see.AnalyticsLike many other websites we track visits to our website using Google Analytics. This data helps us to pick up problems and optimise this website to be as useful to our visitors as possible.Data collected can include information about your computer, about your visits to and use of this website, your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views. However, all this information is anonymised by Google as soon as technically feasible and we are unable to identify individual visitors through Google Analytics data alone.You can find Google’s privacy policy here.Who we share your data withWe do not and never will sell your data to any other company. We will not email you in the future unless you have given us your consent.The providers of analytics tools and external media embedded on this site may use data they collect in order to customise content, including advertisements, that they show to you on other sites, just as they do when you visit those sites (e.g when performing a Google search or watching a YouTube video). If you have a Google account you can opt out of Google’s advertising customisation here.How long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognise and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.What rights you have over your dataIf you have left submitted data to us on this site through e.g comments or our contact form, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataSubmissions of our contact form are emailed to the primary email address for this site shown in the ‘Get in touch offline’ box on the same page, which is checked and responded to by one of our staff members or volunteers. When necessary we’ll then forward your email on to relevant parties proportional to your request.How we protect your dataWhen you load our website the connection is encrypted by a 256bit http-01 SSL security certificate, making data transferred between your router and our servers unintelligible to anyone else, so long as your local device security is adequate. Always check, however, that pages on this site load with a padlock symbol in the top bar just before the URL, or start with “https://”. Please inform us if you ever see otherwise.The transfer of email from this site to our email accounts is also encrypted by a security certificate, but the security of any subsequent forwarding of email is dependent on the security of those respective email services.Questions or requestsIf you have any questions regarding this privacy policy or to request a copy, update or deletion of your data, you may contact us using the contact form in the main menu.
Name
Email Address
Message
Submit
Copyright © 2020 JFCT – Nether Heyford, Northampton, NN7 3LB.
UK Tel: 0845 123 5550 (UK local rate) / +44 1327 344511 (International)Our website uses cookies and by using the site you agree to this.
Read our privacy policy for more info or to learn how to opt out of cookies.
WordPress web design by Lucid Rhino Web Design.Privacy PolicyUsing NCCC ContentSite map
